Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXV is arranged in 83 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXV. AMERICAN FEDERATION OF LABOR AND CONGRESS OF INDUSTRIAL ORGANIZATIONS (AFL-CIO)
  - Sub-Series 271-0. AFL-CIO
    - Committee on International Affairs. Israel, 1958-1959 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Unemployment Conference, 1959 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights Committee. Discrimination, 1957-1959 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights Committee. Special Subcommittee to Review the Memorandum on Civil Rights in the AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 236, Folder 6)
      September 1957-59.
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1957 (Box 236, Folder 7)
      March-August 1957.
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 236, Folder 8)
      1956-February 1957.
    - Community Service, 1964-1965 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Community Service, 1959-1963 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee. United Packinghouse Workers Hearings, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      May 5-7, 1959.
    - Committees on Ethical Practices. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1957-1959 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Bakers' Union, 1957-1959 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Committee on International Affairs, 1958-1959 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      December 1958-February 9, 1959.
    - Committee on International Affairs, 1958 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      June 11, 1958-November 1958.
    - Committee on International Affairs, 1958 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      March 1958-June 10, 1958.
    - Committee on International Affairs, 1955-1958 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      1955-February 1958.
    - Committee on International Affairs. International Affairs Bulletin, 1956-1957 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Education, 1959-1962 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      October 1959-May 18, 1962.
    - Committee on Education, 1958-1959 (Box 238, Folder 7)
      January 11, 1958-September 1959.
    - Committee on Education, 1957-1958 (Box 238, Folder 8)
      February 1957-January 10, 1958.
    - Committee on Education, 1956-1957 (Box 238, Folder 9)
      October 14, 1956-January 1957.
    - Committee on Education, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 10)
      January 1956-October 13, 1956.
    - Committee on Education, 1954-1955 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Education, 1949-1953 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Ethical Practices. Allied Distillery-Laundry. Hearings, 1955-1956 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Economic Policy, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      March-April 1957.
    - Committee on Economic Policy, 1956-1957 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Waste Material Handlers. Paul Dorfman, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Building Service, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Can Workers, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Transport Workers, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Railroads, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Laundry Workers' International Union, 1956-1957 (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Allied Industrial Workers' Union, 1956-1957 (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Jewelry Workers, 1958 (Box 239, Folder 12)
      February-July 1958.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices March 11, 1958-December 1958 (Box 239, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices, 1957-1958 (Box 239, Folder 14)
      October 21, 1957-March 10, 1958.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 15)
      June 18, 1957-October 20, 1957.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices, 1957 (Box 239, Folder 16)
      January 22, 1957-June 17, 1957.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices, 1956-1957 (Box 239, Folder 17)
      1956-January 21, 1957.
    - Pension Committee, 1956 (Box 239, Folder 18)
    - Joint Policy Committee, 1955 (Box 239, Folder 19)
    - American Federation of Labor (AFL). General, 1940-1943 (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - AFL. General, 1942 (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - AFL. General, 1926-1930 (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - AFL. General, 1931 (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - AFL. General, 1930 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - AFL Samuel Gompers Centennial Dinner, 1950 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Constitution, 1955 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - General, 1958 (Box 240, Folder 7)
      May 1958-August 2, 1958.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 240, Folder 8)
      August 1957-April 1958.
    - General, 1957 (Box 240, Folder 9)
      January-July 1957.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 240, Folder 10)
      December 1955-December 1956.
    - AFL. General, 1955 (Box 240, Folder 11)
      June-November 1955.
    - AFL. General, 1944-1945 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - AFL. General, 1954-1955 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      September 1954-May 1955.
    - General, 1954 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      February-August 1954.
    - AFL. General, 1953 (Box 241, Folder 4)
      March 1953-October 22, 1953.
    - AFL. General, 1952-1953 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      January 1952-February 1953.
    - AFL. General, 1953-1954 (Box 241, Folder 6)
      October 23, 1953-January 1954.
    - AFL. General, 1950-1951 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      October 1950-51.
    - AFL. General, 1949-1950 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      November 1949-September 1950.
    - AFL. General, 1948-1949 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      July 1948-October 1949.
    - AFL. General, 1948 (Box 241, Folder 4)
      January-June 1948.
    - AFL. General, 1946-1947 (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - AFL. General, 1933-1939 (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - AFL. National Farm Labor Union, 1947-1953 (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - AFL. Samuel Gompers Centennial Celebration Dinner, 1949-1950 (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - AFL. Proceedings, 1949 (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      1963-February 1964.
    - General, 1962 (Box 242, Folder 2)
      March-December 1962.
    - General, 1960 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - General, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      August 3, 1959-December 1959.
    - General, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 5)
      February 11, 1959-July 1959.
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 242, Folder 6)
      August 3, 1958-February 10, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 271-1. AFL-CIO. Conventions
    - Fifth Constitutional Convention, 1963 (Box 242, Folder 7)
      1963 November, 14
    - 1961 Convention (Box 242, Folder 8)
      December 7-17, 1961.
    - 1959 Convention (Box 242, Folder 9)
      September 17-25, 1959.
    - Resolutions, 1958-1959 (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - AFL. Conventions, 1921 (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-4. AFL
    - Organizers' Commissions, 1932-1951 (Box 242, Folder 12)
    - Organizers' Commissions, 1921-1931 (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 271-5. AFL
    - 1921 Convention (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 271-6. AFL-CIO
    - Maritime Trades Department, 1962-1963 (Box 242, Folder 15)
    - AFL. Maritime Trades Department, 1921 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-7. AFL-CIO
    - Central Labor Councils, 1952-1957 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      March 1952-57.
    - AFL. Central Labor Councils, 1949-1952 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      September 1949-February 1952.
    - AFL. Central Labor Councils, 1947-1949 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      1947-August 1949.
    - AFL. Central Labor Councils, 1944-1946 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - AFL. Central Labor Councils, 1940-1943 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - AFL. Central Labor Councils, 1935-1939 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - AFL. Central Labor Councils, 1921-1925 (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 271-8. AFL
    - International Workers of the World. "One Big Union", 1921 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 271-9. AFL
    - 271-9. AFL. Per Capita Tax, 1934-1953 (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Per Capita Tax, 1921-1933 (Box 243, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-10. AFL
    - Organizers, 1921-1931 (Box 243, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 271-11. AFL
    - Resolutions, 1921-1925 (Box 243, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 271-12. AFL
    - American Federationist, 1930-1955 (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - American Federationist, 1947 (Box 243, Folder 15)
    - American Federationist, 1921-1929 (Box 243, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 271-13. AFL
    - Legal Information, 1925 (Box 243, Folder 17)
    - Legal Information, 1921-1924 (Box 243, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 271-14. AFL-CIO
    - Statements of Executive Council, 1965 (Box 243, Folder 19)
    - Statements of Executive Council, 1963-1964 (Box 243, Folder 20)
    - Statements of Executive Council, 1962 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Statements of Executive Council, 1960-1961 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Statements of Executive Council, 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 3)
      October 1958-59.
    - Executive Council, 1961-1963 (Box 244, Folder 4)
      June 1961-March 14, 1963.
    - Executive Council, 1960-1961 (Box 244, Folder 5)
      1960-May 1961.
    - Executive Council, 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Executive Council, 1957-1958 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      November 1957-September 1958.
    - Executive Council, 1955-1957 (Box 244, Folder 8)
      December 1955-October 1957.
    - AFL. Executive Council, 1951-1955 (Box 244, Folder 9)
      1951-November 1955.
    - AFL. Executive Council, 1935-1950 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - AFL. Executive Council, 1921-1932 (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-15. AFL
    - Expenses of Brotherhood Delegates, 1922 (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 271-16. AFL
    - Instructions, 1922-1930 (Box 244, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 271-17. AFL
    - Charters, 1919-1923 (Box 244, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 271-18. AFL
    - 1923 Convention. Credentials (Box 244, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 271-19. AFL
    - 1924 Convention (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-20. AFL
    - Organization of Women Workers, 1926 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 271-21. AFL
    - Labor Information, 1924-1934 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 271-22. AFL
    - Friends of Mexico Committee, 1924 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 271-23. AFL
    - Political Program, 1924-1947 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-24. AFL
    - Group Insurance, 1924-1925 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 271-25. AFL
    - Unfair Concerns, 1925 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 271-26. AFL
    - Samuel Gompers Memorial, 1929 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 271-27. AFL
    - 1926 Convention, 1925 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 271-28. AFL
    - Financial Statement, 1924 (Box 245, Folder 6)
      1924 February 28
  - Sub-Series 271-29. AFL
    - Organization, 1947-1961 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - AFL-CIO. Organizational Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Organization Campaign, 1933-1946 (Box 245, Folder 9)
      1933-May 19, 1946.
    - Organization Campaign, 1946 (Box 245, Folder 10)
      May 20, 1946-December 1946.
    - Organization Campaign, 1925-1932 (Box 245, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-30. AFL
    - Negotiation, 1925 (Box 245, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 271-31. AFL
    - Credentials, 1925 (Box 245, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 271-32. AFL
    - Voluntary Organizers, 1925-1929 (Box 245, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 271-33. AFL
    - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1953-1956 (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1950-1952 (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1944-1949 (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1933-1943 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1929-1931 (Box 245, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 271-34. AFL
    - Report of Executive Council, 1926 (Box 245, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 271-36. AFL
    - Local Lodge Affiliations, 1925 (Box 245, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 271-37. AFL
    - Convention, 1928 (Box 245, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 271-38. AFL
    - National Law Enforcement Commission, 1929 (Box 245, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 271-39. AFL
    - Convention, 1929 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-40. AFL
    - Publications, 1929-1934 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 271-41. AFL
    - Communists, 1929-1934 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 271-42. AFL
    - Chief Executives' Conference, 1934 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 271-43. AFL
    - Unemployment, 1929 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 271-44. AFL
    - Convention, 1930 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 271-45. AFL
    - Immigration, 1930 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 271-46. AFL
    - American Labor Banner, 1930 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 271-47. AFL
    - Notes for Speakers, 1930-1932 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 271-48. AFL-CIO
    - General, 1930-1959 (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 271-49. AFL
    - Charts, 1929 (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-50. AFL
    - Convention, 1931 (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 271-51. AFL
    - Golden Jubilee, 1931 (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 271-52. AFL
    - Brotherhood Records, 1931 (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 271-54. AFL
    - Convention, 1932 (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 271-55. AFL
    - United Action for Employment, 1932 (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 271-56. AFL
    - Chicago Political Conference, 1932 (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 271-57. AFL
    - Labor Planks, 1936 (Box 246, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 271-58. AFL
    - Convention, 1933 (Box 246, Folder 19)
    - Convention, 1934 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-60. AFL-CIO
    - Press Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 247, Folder 2)
      July 1960-June 1961.
    - Press Releases, 1960 (Box 247, Folder 3)
      January-June 1960.
    - Press Releases, 1959 (Box 247, Folder 4)
      February 10, 1959-December 1959.
    - Press Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 247, Folder 5)
      March 1958-February 9, 1959.
    - Press Releases, 1956-1958 (Box 247, Folder 6)
      November 1956-February 1958.
    - Press Releases. Conference News, 1956 (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 8)
      1955-October 1956.
    - AFL. Press Releases, 1953-1955 (Box 247, Folder 9)
      September 1953-55.
    - Press Releases, 1965 (Box 247, Folder 10)
      May-December 1965.
    - Press Releases, 1964-1965 (Box 247, Folder 11)
      January 1964-April 1965.
    - Press Releases, 1963 (Box 247, Folder 12)
      April-December 1963.
    - Press Releases, 1962-1963 (Box 247, Folder 13)
      October 1962-March 1963.
    - Press Releases, 1962 (Box 247, Folder 14)
      May 16, 1962-September 1962.
    - Press Releases, 1962 (Box 247, Folder 15)
      January 1962-May 15, 1962.
    - Subcommittee No. 1. Resolutions, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Resolutions, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Subcommittee No. 2. Resolutions, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 271-61. AFL
    - Convention, 1935 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 271-62. AFL
    - Convention Delegates, 1936 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 271-63. AFL
    - Convention Delegates, 1937 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 271-64. AFL
    - Convention Delegates, 1938 (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 271-65. AFL
    - Maritime Trades Council, 1939-1948 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 271-66. AFL
    - Convention, 1939 (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 271-67. AFL
    - Convention Delegates, 1940 (Box 248, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-68. AFL
    - Convention Delegates, 1941 (Box 248, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 271-69. AFL
    - Conventions, 1942-1944 (Box 248, Folder 13)
    - Convention, 1944 (Box 248, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 271-70. AFL-CIO
    - Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1965 (Box 248, Folder 15)
      May 21-26, 1965.
    - Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1964 (Box 248, Folder 16)
      May 22-27, 1964.
    - Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1963 (Box 248, Folder 17)
      May 17-22, 1963.
    - AFL and AFL-CIO. Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1943-1962 (Box 248, Folder 18)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1935-1942 (Box 248, Folder 19)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 20)
      April 7-12, 1961.
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1957-1958 (Box 248, Folder 21)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 22)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1954-1955 (Box 248, Folder 23)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1952-1954 (Box 248, Folder 24)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1952-1953 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1951 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1949-1950 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1948-1950 (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - AFL. Union Label Trades Department, 1947-1948 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - AFL. Union Industries Show, 1949 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 271-71. AFL
    - Supplemental Retirement Plan, 1944-1956 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 271-72. AFL
    - Convention, 1946 (Box 249, Folder 8-9)
  - Sub-Series 271-73. AFL
    - Labor Press, 1947-1950 (Box 249, Folder 10)
      1947-April 1950.
  - Sub-Series 271-74. AFL
    - Convention Delegates, 1947 (Box 249, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-75. AFL-CIO
    - International Labor Relations Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 249, Folder 12)
      October 1961-December 1962.
    - International Labor Relations Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 249, Folder 13)
      June 1960-September 1961.
    - International Labor Relations Committee, 1960 (Box 249, Folder 14)
      January-May 1960.
    - International Labor Relations Committee, 1959 (Box 249, Folder 15)
      May-December 1959.
    - International Labor Relations Committee, 1947-1959 (Box 249, Folder 16)
      1947-April 1959.
  - Sub-Series 271-76. AFL-CIO
    - Convention, 1957 (Box 249, Folder 17)
    - Convention, 1955 (Box 249, Folder 18)
    - Conventions, 1953-1955 (Box 249, Folder 19)
    - AFL. Conventions, 1948-1952 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-77. AFL
    - National Legislative Council, 1958 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 271-78. AFL
    - International Longshoremen's Association Dispute, 1952-1955 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 271-79. AFL-CIO
    - No-Raiding Agreement, 1957-1961 (Box 250, Folder 4)
      September 1957-November 1961.
    - No-Raiding Agreement, 1955-1957 (Box 250, Folder 5)
      August 1955-August 1957.
    - AFL. No-Raiding Agreement with CIO, 1954-1955 (Box 250, Folder 6)
      August 1954-July 1955.
    - AFL. No-Raiding Agreement with CIO, 1952-1954 (Box 250, Folder 7)
      1952-July 1954.
    - AFL. No-Raiding Agreement with CIO. A.E. Larson Desk File, 1955 (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 271-80. AFL-CIO
    - Internal Disputes Plan, 1955-1960 (Box 250, Folder 9)
      December 1955-60.
    - Internal Disputes Plan, 1953-1955 (Box 250, Folder 10)
      1953-November 1955.
    - Internal Disputes Plan. Air Line Pilots' Association and Flight Engineers' International Association, 1954-1959 (Box 250, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 271-81. AFL-CIO
    - Merger, 1955 (Box 250, Folder 12)
      July-November 1955.
    - Merger, 1952-1955 (Box 250, Folder 13)
      1952-June 1955.
  - Sub-Series 271-82. AFL-CIO
    - Conference of National Organizations, 1958-1959 (Box 251, Folder 1)
      March 4, 1958-59.
    - Conference of National Organizations, 1957-1958 (Box 251, Folder 2)
      March 1957-March 3, 1958.
    - Conference of National Organizations, 1952-1957 (Box 251, Folder 3)
      1952-February 1957.
  - Sub-Series 271-83. AFL-CIO
    - Committee on Political Education, 1962 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Political Education, 1960-1962 (Box 251, Folder 5)
      September 1960-February 1962.
    - Committee on Political Education, 1959-1960 (Box 251, Folder 6)
      October 1959-August 1960.
    - Committee on Political Education, 1957-1959 (Box 251, Folder 7)
      September 1957-September 1959.
    - Committee on Political Education, 1956-1957 (Box 251, Folder 8)
      1956-August 1957.
  - Sub-Series 271-84. AFL-CIO
    - Research Department, 1959-1962 (Box 251, Folder 9)
      September 9, 1959-December 1962.
    - Research Department, 1958-1959 (Box 251, Folder 10)
      1958-September 8, 1959.
    - Research Department, 1956-1957 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 271-86. AFL-CIO
    - Economic and Legislative Conference, 1962 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      January 22-25, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 271-87. AFL-CIO
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1958 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Carpenters, 1957-1959 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Distillery, Rectifying, and Wine Workers International Union, 1956-1957 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Electrical Workers, 1957-1959 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. The Hotel and Restaurant Workers and Bartenders International Union, 1958 (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, 1958-1961 (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1960 (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. International Union of Operating Engineers, 1958-1959 (Box 252, Folder 10)
      July 1958-59.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. International Union of Operating Engineers, 1956-1958 (Box 252, Folder 11)
      1956-June 1958.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Jewelry Workers, 1958-1961 (Box 252, Folder 12)
      August 1958-61.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. National Federation of Post Office Clerks, 1959 (Box 252, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Packing House Workers, 1959-1961 (Box 252, Folder 14)
      August 1959-61.
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Pattern Makers, 1958 (Box 252, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1959 (Box 252, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. United Textile Workers, 1957-1958 (Box 252, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Ethical Practices. Upholsterers Union, 1959-1960 (Box 252, Folder 18)
      October 1959-60.
  - Sub-Series 271-88. AFL-CIO
    - Advisory Committee on Foreign Trade Policy, 1960-1961 (Box 252, Folder 19)
      January 1960-61.